Norman mss. III, 1958-1983 LMC 2668
Lilly Library
- Correspondence, 1950-1981 (Box 12)
  - Legal, 1974-1977 (Box 16)
    - "Lawyers - Bad News", 1974-1977 (Box 16)
- Photographs, 1950-1980 (Box 14)
  - The Last Banana Skin Photographs 1/4, 1950-1980 (Box 6)
  - The Last Banana Skin Photographs 2/4, 1950-1980 (Box 6)
  - The Last Banana Skin Photographs 3/4, 1950-1980 (Box 6)
  - The Last Banana Skin Photographs 4/4, 1950-1980 (Box 6)
  - Photographs c1950s-1981 1/2, 1950-1980 (Box 14)
  - Photographs c1950s-1981 2/2, 1950-1980 (Box 14)
  - "Street Scenes", 1950-1980 (Box 14)
  - "People", 1950-1980 (Box 14)
  - "Theater", 1950-1980 (Box 14)
  - Photo - Unidentified Person (Ovflat 37)
  - Fragile Photo - Frank and Unknown Subject (Ovflat 37)
- Miscellaneous, 1957-1981 (Box 14)
  - Address Book (Box 14)
  - Cash Book (Box 14)
  - Appointment Book, 1957 (Box 14)
  - Driver's License 1978 (Box 14)
  - Fings Ain't Wot They Used T'Be Commemorative Wallet (Box 14)
  - Dust Jackets, 1958-1981 (Box 14)
  - Flook Comic Scrapbook (Box 14)
  - Omega Watch Pamphlet, 1980 (Box 14)
  - Ephemera (Box 14)
  - Black Notebook with Red Binding (Box 16)
  - Black Notebook (Box 16)
  - Lion Brand Notebook (Box 16)
  - Marble Cover Notebook (Box 16)
  - Checkbook (Box 17)
- Audio/Visual (Box 15)
  - 26 Audio Cassettes (Box 15)